<?xml version='1.0'?>

<project>
   
	<name>ORB-SLAM</name>

   <author>
		<name>Raul Mur-Artal</name>
		<url>http://webdiis.unizar.es/~raulmur</url>
	</author>
        <author>
		<name>J. M. M. Montiel</name>
		<url>http://webdiis.unizar.es/~josemari</url>
	</author>
        <author>
		<name>Juan D. Tardos</name>
		<url>http://webdiis.unizar.es/~jdtardos</url>
	</author>

   <url>http://webdiis.unizar.es/~raulmur/orbslam</url>

   <briefdescription>
	 ORB-SLAM is a keyframe and feature-based Monocular SLAM. It operates in real-time in large environments, being able to close loops
    and perform camera relocalisation from very different viewpoints.
	</briefdescription>

   <description>
	ORB-SLAM is a versatile and accurate Monocular SLAM solution able to compute in real-time the camera trajectory 
	and a sparse 3D reconstruction of the scene in a wide variety of environments, ranging from small hand-held sequences 
	to a car driven around several city blocks. It is able to close large loops and perform global relocalisation 
	in real-time and from wide baselines. It includes an automatic and robust initialization from planar and non-planar scenes.
	A novel survival of the fittest keyframe selection allows to maintain a compact map, while improving the tracking robustness as keyframes
	are inserted very fast during exploration.
	</description>

   <requirement>
	Tested in Ubuntu 12.04
	</requirement>      
	<requirement>
	ROS (tested with Fuerte, Groovy and Hydro), Boost, BLAS, LAPACK and CHOLMOD
	</requirement>

	<map>Sparse 3D points, keyFrame poses and covisibility graph</map>

	<input>Monochrome/Color Images</input>

	<paper>
		<title>ORB-SLAM: a Versatile and Accurate Monocular SLAM</title>
		<authorlist>Raul Mur-Artal, J. M. M. Montiel and Juan D. Tardos</authorlist>
		<publishedin>IEEE Transactions on Robotics, under review. ArXiv preprint</publishedin>
		<year>2015</year>
		<url>http://arxiv.org/abs/1502.00956</url>
	</paper>
		
	<license> 
ORB-SLAM is released under a GPLv3 license.
For a closed-source version of ORB-SLAM for commercial purposes, please contact the authors.

ORB-SLAM is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.</license>



</project>
